http://www.practiceconcepts.com/privacy-policy-216

Client Dropbox
Practice Concepts Privacy Practice Concepts ("PC") is committed to respecting your privacy. Please read the following policy to understand how your information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This policy will let you know the following: 1. What identifiable information is collected?On some Practice Concepts Web pages you can make requests and/or receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are your name, e-mail address and standard contact information, including addresses and phone numbers.
We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with the services we provide and contact preferences. Wherever Practice Concepts collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. WE NEVER SHARE THIS INFORMATION WITH ANYONE OR ANY OTHER COMPANY WITHOUT YOUR EXPRESS PERMISSION 2. How is my information used? Practice Concepts will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. The information you provide will be used to support your customer relationship with Practice Concepts. Your information may be shared with our employees, agents, contractors or business partners for the purpose of performing services for Practice Concepts and yourself.
We want to help you quickly find information on Practice Concepts and alert you to specific offers, updated information, and other new products and services from Practice Concepts. Accordingly, we, if you agree, may send you direct emails or contact you by telephone about our various products and services or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. You can always "opt-out" at anytime. 3. Links and other online resourcesWhen you are on a Practice Concepts site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Practice Concepts alone, unless specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than Practice Concepts you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. Please be aware that Practice Concepts advertisers or vendors that may be listed on our website may have links to their own sites.
The practices of those web sites linked or listed on Practice Concepts' websites are not covered by this privacy statement. 4. We don't share or sell your informationWe do not share your personal data with anyone else other than Practice Concepts employees, agents, contractors, lenders or our business partners for the purposes of performing services for you. We will not share or sell your personal information with other companies for marketing purposes.
All personal information obtained from you is kept in the strictest of confidence.
We recognize that potential buyers and sellers wish to maintain the highest level of confidentiality to protect their business goodwill or employment situation.
We will never disclose to another party the name of a potential buyer or seller without your permission.
HomeAbout PCContact UsPrivacy PolicyBlogTerms of Use
©2010 - 2020 Practice Concepts. All rights reserved.
